Guide to the Leonard Jimmie Savage Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1946-1972; Series I; 15 linear feet (34 boxes)
  - Craig, Cecil Calvert (3), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - Cramer, Harald (1), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - D (15), 1952, 1958, 1960, 1963, 1968-1971, undated (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Daboni, Luciano (9), 1959, 1961, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - Dalenius, Tore (3), 1962 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Dall'Aglio, Giorgio (19), 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - D'Ambrosio, Charles A. (2), 1965, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Daniel, Cuthbert (1), 1964 (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - Daniel, Klaus (2), 1963 (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Daniels, Henry E. (3), 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Daniere, A. (1), 1962 (Box 66A, Folder 26)
  - Dantzig, George Bernard (2), 1960, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 177)
  - Darling, Donald Allan (7), 1957, 1959-1960, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - Darling, Donald Allen (2), 1963 (Box 66A, Folder 27)
  - Darmois, G. (2), 1951 (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Darst, Richard B. (2), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - David, Herbert T. (14), 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 180)
  - Davis, H. Chandler (10), 1955, 1958, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 181)
  - Dawes, Robyn Mason (1), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 182)
  - Day, Mahlon Marsh (7), 1959-1960, 1963, undated (Box 7, Folder 183)
  - Debreu, Gerard (3), 1961 (Box 7, Folder 184)
  - Debreu, Gerard (2), 1969 (Box 66A, Folder 28)
  - De Carlo, Charles (1), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 185)
  - De Carolis, Linda (4), 1962 (Box 7, Folder 185)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (27), 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 186)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (16), 1952-1954 (Box 7, Folder 187)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (36), 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 188)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (43), 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 189)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (51), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 190)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (48), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 191)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (49), 1961 January-June (Box 7, Folder 192)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (40), 1961 July-December (Box 7, Folder 193)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (40), 1962 January-July (Box 8, Folder 194)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (23), 1962 August-December (Box 8, Folder 195)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (27), 1963 January-April (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (32), 1963 May-December (Box 8, Folder 197)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (45), 1964 (Box 8, Folder 198)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (33), 1965 (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (27), 1966 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (35), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 201)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (10), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 202)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (24), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 203)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (24), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 204)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (28), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - de Finetti, Bruno (8), 1958, 1963-1966 (Box 66A, Folder 29)
  - de Grazia, Alfred (3), 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 206)
  - de Groot, Morris Herman (28), 1957, 1960-1962, 1966, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 207)
  - De Groot, Morris Herman (8), 1961-1963, 1966 (Box 66A, Folder 30)
  - Deitrick, John E.
    See: box 33, folder 804
  - de Jouvenel, Bertrand (4), 1962, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 208)
  - DeLong, Arthur R., 1967 (Box 66A, Folder 31)
  - Deming, William Edwards (4), 1945, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Dempster, Arthur Pentland (2), 1961 (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Dempster, Arthur Pentland (6), 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 211)
  - Dempster, Arthur Pentland (4), 1964 (Box 8, Folder 212)
  - Dempster, Arthur Pentland (7), 1965 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Dempster, Arthur Pentland (6), 1966, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 214)
  - Dempster, Arthur Pentland (5), 1966, 1969, 1971 (Box 66A, Folder 32)
  - Diamond, Gerald X. (3), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 215)
  - Di Cesare, D. A. (11), 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 216)
  - Dickey, James M. (25), 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 217)
  - Dickey, James M. (20), 1965 (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Dickey, James M. (30), 1966-1971, undated (Box 9, Folder 219)
  - Dickey, James M. (32), 1963-1969, 1971 (Box 66A, Folder 34)
  - Dieckmann, William J. (4), 1949-1950, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 220)
  - Dodge, Linwood W. (4), 1965 (Box 66A, Folder 33)
  - Doob, Joseph Lee (2), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Douglas, James B. (20), 1961-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 222)
  - Douglas, Paul Howard (3), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 223)
  - Dover Publications, Inc. (5), 1950 (Box 9, Folder 224)
  - Dover Publications, Inc. (34), 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 225)
  - Drenick, Rudolph F. (25), 1954-1956, 1960-1962 (Box 9, Folder 226)
  - Dreze, Jacques H. (16), 1957-1958, 1966, 1971, undated (Box 9, Folder 227)
  - Dubins, Julius (24), 1963-1964, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 228)
  - Dubins, Lester Eli (29), 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 229)
  - Dubins, Lester Eli (16), 1958 October-December (Box 9, Folder 230)
  - Dubins, Lester Eli (15), 1959 January-February (Box 9, Folder 231)
  - Dubins, Lester Eli (13), 1959 March (Box 9, Folder 232)
  - Dubins, Lester Eli (8), 1959 April-May (Box 10, Folder 233)
  - Dubins, Lester Eli (33), 1959 September-December (Box 10, Folder 234)
  - Dubins, Lester Eli (12), 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 235)
  - Dubins, Lester Eli (47), 1963 (Box 10, Folder 236)
  - Dubins, Lester Eli (29), 1964 January-March (Box 10, Folder 237)
  - Dubins, Lester Eli (30), 1964 April-December (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Dubins, Lester Eli (30), 1965 January-April (Box 10, Folder 239)
  - Dubins, Lester Eli (56), 1965 May-1971, undated (Box 10, Folder 240)
  - Dubins, Lester Eli (5), 1959, 1963 (Box 66A, Folder 35)
  - Du Mouchel, William H.(35), 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 241)
  - Duncan, David Beattie(3), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 242)
  - Duncan, George Thomas (2), 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 242)
  - Durbin, James (26), 1960, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 243)
  - Dutton, Richard (4), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 244)
  - Dwass, Meyer (5), 1962 (Box 10, Folder 245)
  - Dwass, Meyer (2), 1956 (Box 66A, Folder 36)
  - Dwyer, John M. (1), undated (Box 10, Folder 245)
  - Dwyer, Paul Sumner (10), 1961, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 246)
  - Dwyer, Paul Sumner (1), 1962 (Box 66A, Folder 36)
  - Dyen, Isidore (4), 1965, 1970, undated (Box 10, Folder 247)
  - Dynkin, E. E. (6), 1955, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 248)
  - E (7), 1964, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 249)
  - The Econometric Society (10), 1951, 1955, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Edwards, Ward (16), 1954-1956 (Box 11, Folder 251)
  - Edwards, Ward (16), 1958-1962 (Box 11, Folder 252)
  - Edwards, Ward (18), 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 253)
  - Edwards, Ward (12), 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 254)
  - Edwards, Ward (7), 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 255)
  - Edwards, Ward (6), 1964, 1965 (Box 66A, Folder 37)
  - Eells, Liese (1), 1966 (Box 66A, Folder 36)
  - Efron, Bradley (13), 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 256)
  - Eisenhart, Churchill (6), 1957, 1961, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - Elashoff, Robert M. (3), 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 258)
  - Elfving, Gustav (20), 1955-1956, 1959, 1961, 1966-1967, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 259)
  - Ellsberg, Daniel (7), 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 260)
  - Elston, Robert C. (4), 1966 (Box 66A, Folder 37)
  - Ericson, William Arnold (16), 1962-1963, 1965, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 261)
    See also: box 69
  - Ericson, William Arnold (8), 1962, 1964 (Box 66A, Folder 38)
  - F (14), 1955-1957, 1961-1963, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 262)
  - Farrell, Roger Hamlin (4), 1959, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Feder, Paul (6), 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 264)
  - Feferman, Sol (4), 1969 (Box 11, Folder 265)
  - Feller, William (24), 1950-1951, 1954, 1956-1957, 1962, 1965-1966, 1968 undated (Box 11, Folder 266)
  - Fellner, William John (12), 1962-1964, 1966, undated (Box 11, Folder 267)
  - Feraud, L. (3), 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 268)
  - Ferguson, Thomas S. (4), 1963 (Box 11, Folder 269)
  - Fienberg, Stephen E.
    See: box 69
  - Fife, Paul C. (29), 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 270)
  - Finch, Henry Albert (12), 1956, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 271)
  - Fine, Terrence (19), 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 272)
  - Finney, D. J. (3), 1959 (Box 66A, Folder 39)
  - Fishburn, Peter C. (28), 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 273)
  - Fishburn, Peter C. (20), 1966 (Box 12, Folder 274)
  - Fishburn, Peter C. (26), 1967 (Box 12, Folder 275)
  - Fishburn, Peter C. (17), 1968-1971, undated (Box 12, Folder 276)
  - Fishburn, Peter C. (2), 1969-1970 (Box 66A, Folder 40)
  - Fischer, Janos (41), 1965-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Fisher, Ronald Aylmer (15), 1952-1953, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 278)
  - Fisher, Walter D. (33), 1953, 1957, 1959-1962 (Box 12, Folder 279)
  - Fisher, Walter D. (3), 1953, 1959 (Box 66A, Folder 41)
  - Flammarion, Ernest (4), 1962 (Box 12, Folder 280)
  - Flexner, William Welch (7), 1965, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 281)
  - Flood, Merrill Meeks (33), 1950-1955, 1960, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 282)
  - The Ford Foundation (27), 1957, 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 283)
  - The Ford Foundation (14), 1963-1964, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 284)
  - The Ford Foundation, financial materials (Box 12, Folder 285-286)
  - Forsyth, Louise (27), 1955, 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 287)
  - Forsyth, Louise (28), 1963-1965, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 288)
  - Forsyth, Louise (18), 1960, 1962-1964 (Box 66A, Folder 42)
  - Franco Angeli Editore (4), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 289)
  - Fraser, Donald Alexander Stuart (15), 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 290)
  - Frechet, Maurice (34), 1951-1956 (Box 13, Folder 291)
  - Frechet, Maurice (19), 1960-1961, 1963, 1966-1967, 1970, undated (Box 13, Folder 292)
  - Freedman, David A. (34), 1961-1963, 1966, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 293)
  - Freedman, David (7), 1963, 1966, 1969 (Box 66A, Folder 43)
  - Freemen, Harold (6), 1961, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 294)
  - Fremont-Smith, Frank (5), 1959, 1964, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 295)
  - Freund, John Ernst (1), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 296)
  - Friedell, Morris F. (3), 1967 (Box 13, Folder 297)
  - Friedman, Milton R. (2), 1964, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 298)
  - Fulbright Scholarships (6), 1956-1958 (Box 13, Folder 299)
  - Fultz, Dave (3), 1962 (Box 13, Folder 300)
  - Furst, Dario (40), 1959, 1961-1962, 1963, 1966-1971 (Box 13, Folder 301)
  - Furst, Dario (4), 1969-1970 (Box 66A, Folder 44)
  - G (16), 1958-1961, 1966-1967, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 302)
  - Gabor, André (2), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 303)
  - Gale, David (13), 1957-1958, 1964, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 304)
  - Garding, Lars (3), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 305)
  - Gasser, Herbert Spencer (1), 1945 (Box 13, Folder 306)
  - Gastworth, Joseph L. (4), 1966-1967 (Box 66A, Folder 45)
  - Gebhardt, Friedrich (14), 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 307)
  - Genensky, Samuel Milton (8), 1968, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 308)
  - General Electric Company (1), 1943 (Box 13, Folder 309)
  - General Motors Corporation (14), 1968-1971 (Box 13, Folder 310)
  - Georgia, University of (5), 1967 (Box 13, Folder 311)
  - Gerlach, Muriel Wood (2), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 312)
  - Ghurye, S. G. (15), 1955-1956, 1959 (Box 66A, Folder 46)
  - Giere, Ronald N. (9), 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 313)
  - Giere, Ronald N. (1), 1969 (Box 66A, Folder 46)
  - Gilat, David (4), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 314)
  - Gilbert, John P. (8), 1957-1958, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 315)
  - Gilbert, John P. (1), 1950 (Box 66A, Folder 47)
  - Girault, Maurice (2), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 316)
  - Giri, N. C. (2), 1967 (Box 66A, Folder 47)
  - Girshick, M. A. (12), 1950-1951, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 317)
  - Givens, Wallace (3), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 318)
  - Glasser, Robert Gene (3), 1956, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 319)
  - Glasser, Robert Gene (2), 1954 (Box 66A, Folder 48)
  - Gleason, Andrew Mattei (5), 1964, 1966, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 320)
  - Godambe, A. V. (2), 1969 (Box 66A, Folder 48)
  - Godambe, V. P. (15), 1965-1966, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 321)
  - Goldberg, Sam
  - Goldgraber, Moshe (1), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 322)
  - Goldman, Jay R. (5), 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 322)
  - Goldsmith, John R.
    See: box 5, folder 110
  - Good, Irving John (47), 1951, 1954-1959 (Box 13, Folder 323)
  - Good, Irving John (33), 1960-1961, 1963-1964, 1967, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 324)
  - Good, Phillip Frey (2), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 325)
  - Goodman, Leo A. (24), 1956, 1958-1959, 1962-1964, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 326)
  - Gordon, Charles K., Jr. (3), 1963 (Box 14, Folder 327)
  - Gordon Research Conferences (9), 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 328)
  - Gottlieb, Morris Joseph (2), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 329)
  - Graham, R. L. (10), 1963 (Box 14, Folder 329)
  - Gray, Paul (16), 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 330)
  - Graybill, Franklin A. (4), 1967 (Box 14, Folder 331)
  - Graybill, Franklin A. (1), Undated (Box 66A, Folder 49)
  - Greene, Peter H. (3), 1951 (Box 66A, Folder 49)
  - Gregg, John R. (3), 1955 (Box 14, Folder 332)
  - Grenander, Ulf (2), 1966 (Box 14, Folder 332)
  - Gringorten, Irving I. (6), 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 333)
  - Gross, Oliver (7), 1950-1952, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 334)
  - Grunbaum, Adolf (10), 1963, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 335)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (38), 1951, 1953-1954, 1957-1958, 1961, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 336)
  - Guilbaud, G. T. (2), 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 337)
  - Guiraum Martin, Alfonso (2), 1970 (Box 14, Folder 337)
  - Gunther, Paul (10), 1956, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 338)
  - Gunther, Paul (13), 1953-1954 (Box 66A, Folder 50)
  - Gupta, J. C. (1), 1970 (Box 66A, Folder 51)
  - Gupta, Shanti S. (3), 1967, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 339)
  - Guttman, Irwin (8), 1963 (Box 14, Folder 340)
  - Guttman, Irwin (2), 1968 (Box 66A, Folder 51)
  - Guzzi, R. Giuseppe (4), 1953, 1955, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 341)
  - H (35), 1954-1955, 1958, 1960-1967, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 342)
  - Hacking, Ian (22), 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 343)
  - Hacking, Ian (1), 1970 (Box 66B, Folder 52)
  - Hafner Publishing Company (9), 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 344)
  - Hajek, Jaroslav (18), 1963, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 345)
  - Hall, Marshall, Jr. (3), 1970 (Box 14, Folder 346)
  - Hall, William Jackson (30), 1965-1967, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 347)
  - Halmos, Paul Richard (22), 1939, 1947-1948, 1957-1958, 1960-1962, 1964, 1970-1971, n. d. (Box 15, Folder 348)
  - Halmos, Paul Richard (8), 1955, 1958, 1960, 1962, 1971, undated (Box 66B, Folder 52)
  - Halpern, Elkan (3), 1971 (Box 15, Folder 349)
  - Hammer, Preston Clarence (2), 1971 (Box 15, Folder 349)
  - Hannan, E. J. (4), 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 350)
  - Hanson, David Lee
    See: box 32, folder 758
  - Hanurav, R. V. (7), 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 351)
  - Hanurav, R. V. (1), 1968 (Box 66B, Folder 53)
  - Harrell, Cleon (2), 1954 (Box 15, Folder 352)
  - Harrell, Cleon (5), 1950-1951, undated (Box 66B, Folder 53)
  - Harris, Bernard (2), 1963 (Box 15, Folder 352)
  - Harris, Theodore Edward (39), 1956-1957, 1959-1962, 1964-1965, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 353)
  - Harrison, Stephen (2), 1958 (Box 15, Folder 354)
  - Hart, Albert Gailord (2), 1951 (Box 15, Folder 354)
  - Hartigan, John A. (17), 1963, 1966, 1969-1971, n. d. (Box 15, Folder 355)
  - Hartley, Herman Otto (5), 1960, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 356)
  - Harvard University (2), 1946 (Box 15, Folder 357)
  - Harvard University (4), 1966, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 358)
  - Harvard University Press (3), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 358)
  - Harvey, Charles (2), 1970 (Box 66B, Folder 54)
  - Hastay, Millard (4), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 359)
  - Hastay, Millard (2), 1958 (Box 66B, Folder 54)
  - Hastings, Cecil, Jr. (18), 1951-1952, 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 360)
  - Hastings, Cecil, Jr. (24), 1957-1960, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 361)
  - Hastings, Cecil, Jr. (31), 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 362)
  - Hastings, Cecil, Jr. (4), 1966, undated (Box 15, Folder 363)
  - Hastings, Cecil (21), 1965-1968 (Box 66B, Folder 55)
  - Hay, George Edward (40), 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 364)
  - Hay, George Edward (17), 1961-1964 (Box 66B, Folder 56)
  - Heims, Steve P. (5), 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 365)
  - Heiny, Richard Lloyd (4), 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 366)
  - Helmer, Olaf (25), 1951, 1960, 1963, 1965-1968, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 367)
  - Hempel, Carl Gustav (6), 1951, 1965, 1967, undated (Box 15, Folder 368)
  - Herman, Janet B. (3), 1966 (Box 66B, Folder 57)
  - Herman, Louis M. (1), 1965 (Box 66B, Folder 57)
  - Hewitt, Edwin (46), 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 369)
  - Hewitt, Edwin (19), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 370)
  - Hewitt, Edwin (33), 1955 January-April (Box 16, Folder 371)
  - Hewitt, Edwin (30), 1955 May-November (Box 16, Folder 372)
  - Hewitt, Edwin (46), 1956, 1958-1959, 1960-1964, 1966-1967, 1971, undated (Box 16, Folder 373-374)
  - Hewitt, Edwin (2), 1954, 1960 (Box 66B, Folder system_indicator_6ceb73a3c42953993c5ad90ea5caa57d)
  - Hicks, J. S. (7), 1953-1954 (Box 16, Folder 375)
  - Hildebrandt, Theophil Henry (11), 1941-1942, 1945-1946 (Box 16, Folder 376)
  - Hildreth, Clifford (21), 1960-1963, 1965, 1971, undated (Box 16, Folder 377)
  - Hill, Bruce M. (14), 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 378)
  - Hill, Bruce M. (12), 1966 January-April (Box 16, Folder 379)
  - Hill, Bruce M. (19), 1966 May-September (Box 16, Folder 380)
  - Hill, Bruce M. (9), 1966 October-1967 March (Box 16, Folder 381)
  - Hill, Bruce M. (12), 1967 April-June (Box 16, Folder 382)
  - Hill, Bruce M. (22), 1967 July-1968 (Box 16, Folder 383)
  - Hill, Bruce M. (8), 1963, 1965-1967 (Box 66B, Folder 58)
  - Hirshleifer, Jack (7), 1957, 1961-1962, 1968, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 384)
  - Hodges, Joseph Lawson (34), 1952-1955, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 385)
  - Hodges, Joseph Lawson (10), 1963-1964, 1967, undated (Box 17, Folder 386)
  - Hodges, Paul Chesley(3), 1957 (Box 17, Folder 387)
  - Hoeffding, Wassily (7), 1955, 1962-1964 (Box 17, Folder 388)
  - Hogg, Robert Vincent(6), 1953, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 385)
  - Holden-Day, Inc. (4), 1962 (Box 17, Folder 390)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc. (2), 1960, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 391)
  - Holy Cross, College of (4), 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 392)
  - Honeywell, Inc. (7), 1964 (Box 17, Folder 393)
  - The John Hopkins University (2), 1963 (Box 17, Folder 394)
  - Horsfall, Frank L, undated
  - Houle, Alfred (11), 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 395)
  - Householder, Alston Scott(14), 1949-1951, 1954-1955,1960, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 396)
  - Householder, Alston Scott (1), 1963 (Box 66B, Folder 59)
  - Howard, Ronald Arthur(3), 1964 (Box 17, Folder 397)
  - Huber, Peter J. (3), 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 397)
  - Hudson, Derek John(2), 1964 (Box 17, Folder 398)
  - Hughes, H. K. (2), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 399)
  - Humburg, Jurgen (3), 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 399)
  - Ianizzotto, Lorenzo (7), 1963, 1966, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 400)
  - Ianizzotto, Lorenzo (1), 1963 (Box 66B, Folder 59)
  - Ihm, Peter (5), 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 401)
  - Ikle, Doris (Mrs. Fred Ikle) (7), 1968 (Box 17, Folder 402)
  - Ikle, Fred C. (14), 1957-1958, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 403)
  - Ingle, Dwight Joyce (14), 1956-1957, 1959-1960, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 404)
  - The Institute for Advanced Study (1), 1942 (Box 17, Folder 405)
  - Institute for the Future (11), 1966-1971 (Box 17, Folder 406)
  - Institute of Mathematical Statistics (7), 1955-1956, 1958, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 407)
  - Institute of Mathematical Statistics (15), 1953 (Box 66B, Folder 60)
  - Institute of Science and Technology (2), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 408)
  - International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences (13), 1962-1963, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 409)
  - International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences (3), 1967, undated (Box 17, Folder 410)
  - International Mathematical Union (20), 1964-1967, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 411)
  - International Statistical Institute (15), 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 412)
  - Richard D. Irwin, Inc. (2), 1967 (Box 17, Folder 413)
  - Isbell, John Rolfe (8), 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 414)
  - J (2), 1957, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 415)
  - Jacquez, John Alfred (10), 197O-1971 (Box 18, Folder 416)
  - Jaffey, Arthur Harold (14), 1954-1959, undated (Box 18, Folder 417)
  - James, Allan T. (2), 1966 (Box 18, Folder 418)
  - James, R. D. (3), 1958 (Box 18, Folder 418)
  - Jarrett, Rheem F. (2), 1954 (Box 18, Folder 419)
  - Jebe, Emil H. (4), 1961, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 419)
  - Jeffrey, Richard C. (8), 1960, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 420)
  - Jeffrey, Richard C. (22), 1963-1965 (Box 18, Folder 421)
  - Jeffrey, Richard C. (16), 1967-1968, undated (Box 18, Folder 422)
  - Jeffrey, Richard C. (7), 1963, 1968 (Box 66B, Folder 61)
  - Jeffreys, Harold (8), 1936-1938, 1959, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 423)
  - Johnson, N. L. (6), 1963, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 424)
  - Jones, Donald Akers (7), 1962, 1964, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 425)
  - Jones, Ernestine Alice (7), 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 426)
  - Jones, Ernestine Alice, 1963-1964 (Box 66B, Folder 62)
  - Jones, Howard L. (5), 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 426)
  - Joshi, V. M., undated
    See: box 34, folder 826
  - The Journal of Philosophy (10), 1967 (Box 18, Folder 427)
  - K (28), 1955, 1957-1958, 1960-1961, 1963-1964, 1966, 1969-1972 (Box 18, Folder 428)
  - Kac, Mark (4), 1965-1966, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 429)
  - Kadane, Joseph B. (8), 1967-1969, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 430)
  - Kadane, Joseph B. (4), 1968, 1971 (Box 66B, Folder 63)
  - Kahn, Herman (20), 1950, 1954-1957, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 431)
  - Kahn, Herman (2), 1956 (Box 66B, Folder 64)
  - Kaiser, Henry F. (7), 1958-1959, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 432)
  - Kanal, Laveen (5), 1963, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 433)
  - Karlin, Samuel (6), 1954, 1956-1957, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 434)
  - Katz, Leo (2), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 435)
  - Kaufman, Gordon M. (2), 1965 (Box 18, Folder 435)
  - Keeping, E. S. (4), 1962 (Box 18, Folder 436)
  - Kelker, Douglas (4), 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 437)
  - Kemperman, Johannes Henricus Bernardus (11), 1957, 1963, 1965, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 438)
  - Kempthorne, Oscar (13), 1954-1955, 1963, 1967, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 439)
  - Kendall, David G. (17), 1952-1953, 1957-1959, 1965, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 440)
  - Kerrich, John E. (9), 1956, 1961-1963 (Box 18, Folder 441)
  - Kerridge, David (5), 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 442)
  - Kiefer, Jack C. (20), 1958-1963, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 443)
  - Kimball, Bradford F. (7), 1956, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 444)
  - Kimpton, Lawrence A. (4), 1957, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 445)
  - King, E. S. J. (2), 1956 (Box 19, Folder 446)
  - Kingman, John Frank Charles (3), 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 446)
  - Kish, Leslie A. (11), 1954, 1958, 1960-1961, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 447)
  - Kish, Leslie A. (15), 1965, 1969-1971, undated (Box 19, Folder 448)
  - Kish, Leslie (2), 1961 (Box 66B, Folder 64)
  - Kissler, Herbert F. (5), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 449)
  - Kitagawa, Tosio (13), 1953-1955 (Box 19, Folder 450)
  - Klee, Jim (1), 1964 (Box 66B, Folder 64)
  - Kligerman, Morton M. (17), 1966-1968 (Box 19, Folder 451)
  - Kolin, Alexander (2), 1955 (Box 19, Folder 452)
  - Kolin, Alexander (8), 1955-1956 (Box 66B, Folder 65)
  - Komm, Horace (3), 1949, 1956, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 452)
  - Koopman, Bernard Osgood (4), 1950-1951 (Box 19, Folder 453)
  - Koopmans, Tjalling Charles (7), 1949, 1955, 1961, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 454)
  - Kornstein, Susan (6), 1970 (Box 19, Folder 455)
  - Kosambi, D. D. (2), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 456)
  - Koslow, Arnold (2), 1964 (Box 19, Folder 456)
  - Kotz, Samuel (26), 1967-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 457)
  - Kott, Michael (1), 1967 (Box 66B, Folder 65)
  - Kraft, Charles H. (12), 1963 (Box 19, Folder 458)
  - Krauss, Peter Hall (5), 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 459)
  - Kretschmer, Albert Emil (7), 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 460)
  - Krishnaiah, Paruchuri Rama (4), 1964 (Box 19, Folder 461)
  - Kruskal, Joseph Bernard, Jr. (27), 1949-1951, 1953, 1965-1967, 1971, undated (Box 19, Folder 462)
  - Kruskal, Joseph Bernard (8), 1949-1951, 1953-1954 (Box 66B, Folder 66)
  - Kruskal, Martin David (3), 1964, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 463)
  - Kruskal, William Henry (30), 1955-1960 (Box 19, Folder 464)
  - Kruskal, William Henry (45), 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 465)
  - Kruskal, William Henry (36), 1963-1964, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 466)
  - Kruskal, William Henry (31), 1967-1971, undated (Box 19, Folder 467)
  - Kruskal, William Henry (9), 1956, 1958, 1961-1962, 1964, 1966, 1969 (Box 66B, Folder 67)